Guide to the Marvyn Scudder Collection of Corporate Documents,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Alphabetical Files
  - Northern Indiana Public Service Co. - Prospectus TO Northern Pacific Railroad Co. (Box 284)
  - Northern Pacific & Montana Railroad Co. TO Northern State Power Co. TO Northern States Life Insurance Corp. (Box 285)
  - Northern State Power Co. TO Northwestern Bell Telephone Co. (Box 286)
  - Northwestern Fire & Marine Insurance Co. TO Norwalk Iron Works Co. (Box 287)
  - Norwalk Lock Co. To Oceanic Steam Navigation Co., Ltd. (Box 288)
  - Ocilla Southern Railroad TO Ohio Power Co. (Box 289)
  - Ohio Public Service Co TO Oklahoma General Power Co. (Box 290)
  - Oklahoma Iron Works International Supply Co. TO Omaha, Dodge City, and Southern Railway Co. (Box 291)
  - Omaha Horse Railway Co. TO Osage Railway Co. (Box 292)
  - Osage Valley & Southern Kansas Railroad Co. TO Ozark & Cherokee Central Railroad Co. (Box 293)
  - Ozark Corp. TO Pacific Lumber (Box 294)
  - Pacific Lighting TO Palomar Mortgage Co. (Box 295)
  - Pamour Porcupine Mines, Ltd. TO Parbec Mines, Ltd. (Box 296)
  - Pargas, Inc. TO Pecos Valley Power & Light Co. (Box 297)
  - Phelps Dodge Corp. TO Penn-Ohio Edison Co. (Box 298)
  - Penn-Ohio Oil Corp. TO Penn-Ohio Power & Light Co. (Box 299)
  - Penn Power Co. TO Penn Steele (Box 300)
  - Penn Steam Ship CO. TO Peoples Passenger RW CO. (Box 301)
  - Peoples Pertoleum Co. TO Pare Marquette R.R. Co. (Box 302)
  - Pare Marquette R.R. Co. TO Philadelphia & Western Railway CO. (Box 303)
  - Philadelphia, Baltimore & Washington Railroad Co. TO Philadelphia, Reading & New England Railroad Co. (Box 304)
  - Philadelphia Savings Fund Society TO Phoenix Gold Mining Co. (Box 305)
  - Phoenix Gummiwerke A.G. TO Piggly Wiggly Pacific Co., Inc. (Box 306)
  - Piggly Wiggly Stores, Inc. TO Pittsburgh, Binghamton & Eastern Railroad Co. (Box 307)
  - Pittsburgh Board of Trade Land Co. TO Pittsburgh Railways Co. (Box 308)
  - Pittsburgh Real Estate Co. TO Platte Uranium, Inc. (Box 309)
  - Platte Wyoming Oil Co. of Guernsey, Wyoming TO Popular Creek Coal & Iron Co. (Box 310)
  - Porcupine Canadian Goald Mines, Ltd. TO Portland Electric Co. (Box 311)
  - Portland Electric Power Co. TO Postal Telegraph & Cable Corp. (Box 312)
  - Postal Telegraph & Cable Corp TO Power Corporation of Canada, Ltd. (Box 313)
  - Power Corporation of New York TO Preway Inc. (Box 314)
  - Price (Ed.V.) & Co. TO Progressive Laundry & Co. (Box 315)
  - Progress Manufacturing Co. Ltd. TO Prudencia Rebell Cigarette Machine Co. (Box 316)
  - Prudence Securities Corp. TO Public Service Corp. of New Jersey (Box 317)
  - Public Service Corp. of New Jersey TO Public Service Electric & Gas Co. (Box 318)
  - Public Service Electric & Gas Co. TO Puget Sound Bridge and Dredging Co. (Box 319)
  - Puget Sound Construction Co. TO Pyramid Life Insurance Co. (Box 320)
  - Pyramid Mining Co. TO Quincy Station Post Office (Box 321)
  - Quinebaug Co. TO Rainbow Oil & Gas Co. (Box 322)
  - Rainey (Paul J.) Pier Co. TO Raybestos Co. (Box 323)
  - Raybestos-Manhattan, Inc. TO Red Creek & Far Haven Tel. Co. (Box 324)
  - Red Crossgold Mining & Milling Co. TO Reliance Insurance Co. of Philadelphia (Box 325)
  - Reliance International Corp. TO Republic Railway & Light Co. (Box 326)
  - Republic National Bank of New York TO Rez-Tile Industries, Inc. (Box 327)
  - Rezlon Chemical Products Limited TO Richardson & Boynton Co. (Box 328)
  - Richardson (George O.) Machinery Co. TO Ries Biologicals, Inc. (Box 329)
  - Rike-Kumler Co. TO Riverside Trust Co. (Box 330)
  - Riverside Tunnel & Mining Co. TO Rock Island-Frisco Terminal Railway Co. (Box 331)
  - Rock Island Improvement Co. TO Romer Manufacturing Co. (Box 332)
  - Ronalds-Federated Limited TO Ruland and Whiting Co. (Box 333)
  - Rulane Gas Company TO Sackett & Wilhelms Corp. (Box 334)
  - Saco-Lowell Shops TO Saint Joseph Crude Oil & Gas Company (Box 335)
  - Saint Joseph Bridge TO St. Louis & Southeastern Railway Company (Box 336)
  - St. Louis & Springfield Railway Company TO St Louis-San Francisco Railway Co. (Box 337)
  - St. Louis-San Francisco Railway Company TO St. Paul Commercial Building Company (Box 338)
  - St. Paul Construction Company TO San Antonio Machine & Supply Company (Box 339)
  - San Antonio Public Service Company TO Sanders Associates, Inc. (Box 340)
  - Sanford Light & Fuel Co. TO Savings and Loan Bank of the State of New York (Box 341)
  - Savings & Loan Co. TO Schulco Co., Inc. (Box 342)
  - Schulte (D.A.), Inc. TO Scudder Stevens & Clark Common Stock Fund, Inc. (Box 343)
  - Scudder Stevens & Clark Common Stock Fund, Inc. TO Seaboard Petroleum Co (Box 344)
  - Seaboard Oil Co. of Texas TO Second National Bank of Allegheny (Box 345)
  - Second National Bank (Atlantic City) TO Selfridge and Co., Ltd. (Box 346)
  - Selfridge Provincial Stores, Ltd. TO Shamrock Mining Co. (Box 347)
  - Shamrock Oil & Gas Corp. TO Sheffield Farms-Slawson-Decker Co. (Box 348)
  - Sheffield Land & Improvement TO Shetucket Co., Norwich, Conn. (Box 349)
  - Shevlin-Clarke Co., Ltd. TO Silent Writing Machine Co. (Box 350)
  - Silesia Electric Corp. TO Sinclair Consolidated Oil Corp. (Box 351)
  - Sinclair Crude Oil Purchasing Co. TO Smith (W.F.) Co. (Box 352)
  - Smith (A.O.) Mfg. Co. TO Societe Norvegienne de L'azote et du Foreces Hydro-Electrique (Box 353)
  - Societe Pipe-Line Sud-European TO South American Improvement CO. (Box 354)
  - South American Mines CO. TO South Scituate Savings Bank (Box 355)
  - South Shore Club Apts. TO Southern Central Railroad Co. (Box 356)
  - Southern Cities Power Co. TO Southern Indiana Gas & Electric Co. (Box 357)
  - Southern Indiana Railway Co. TO Southern Pacific Lines (Box 358)
  - Southern Pacific RR Co. TO Southern Securities Co. (Box 359)
  - Southern Sierra Power Co TO Speculative Mineral Shares Co. (Box 360)
  - Speed Building To Spang, Chalfant & Co., Inc (Box 361)
  - Spanish American Fruit Co, Inc TO Springfield-Monarch Insurance Companies (Box 362)
  - Springfield Motors Co. TO Standatd Electric Co. Inc. (Box 363)
  - Standard Electric Co. of California TO Standard Oil Co. (KY) (Box 364)
  - Standard Oil Company (Kansasa) TO Stanislaus Farms Co. (Box 365)
  - Stanislaus Power Development Co. TO Stein (A.) & Co. (ILL) (Box 366)
  - Stein-Bloch Co. TO Stone & Webster Inc. (Box 367)
  - Stone & Webster (Street Railway Co) TO Suffern Gas CO. (Box 368)
  - Suffolk & Carolina Railway Co TO Sunroy Oil Corp. (Box 369)
  - Sunroy Oil Corp. TO Sweets Company of America (Box 370)
  - Sweets Steele Company TO Tayloe Pearson & Carson Ltd. (Canada) (Box 371)
  - Taylor Wharton Iron & Steele Co. TO Tennessee Public Service Company (Box 372)
  - Tennessee Railway Light & Power Co. TO Tennessee Natural Gas Lines (Box 373)
  - Texas Eastern Production Co. TO Textron Inc. (Box 374)
  - Textured Fibers Inc. TO Thirteen Hundred and Two Pacific Co. (Box 375)
  - Thriteenth & Chancellor Streets TO Timkin Roller Bearing Co. (Box 376)
  - Timm Aircraft Corp. TO Tonopah & Goldfield RR Company (Box 377)
  - Tonopah Belmont Development Co. TO Trans Mountain Oil Pipe Line Co. (Box 378)
  - Trans Mountain Pipe Line Co., Ltd. TO Tri-Utilities Corp[. (Box 379)
  - Triad Oil Co. TO Tuition Inc. (Box 380)
  - Tularosa Copper Co. TO Underwriter's Securities Corp. TO Union Lumbering Co (Box 381)
  - Underwriter's Securities Corp. TO Union Lumbering Co. (Box 382)
  - Union Metal Manuracturing Co. TO Union Street Railway Co. (Box 383)
  - Union Sugar Co. TO United-Carr Inc. (Box 384)
  - United Central Oil Corp. TO United Electric Service Co. (Box 385)
  - United Electric Traction Co. TO United Gas & Oil Development Co. (Box 386)
  - United Gas Improvement Co. TO United Overseas Bank (Box 387)
  - United Owners Realty CO. TO United Service Co. (Box 388)
  - United Security Life Ins. & Trust Co. TO United States Kings County Bond & Management Corp. (Box 389)
  - United States Leather Co. TO United States Servateria Corp. (Box 390)
  - U.S. Shars Corp. TO U.S. Telephone Mfg. Co. (Box 391)
  - United States Television Mfg. Corp. TO Universal Pictures Co., Inc. (Box 392)
  - Universal Pipe & Radiator Co. TO Utility Equities Corp. (Box 393)
  - Uvava Copper Co. TO Victor Brewing Co. (Box 394)
  - Victor Chemical Works TO Virginia Railway Co. (Box 395)
  - Virginia's Fruie Exchange TO Waco Hilton Hotel Co. (Box 396)
  - Waco Street Ry. TO Wandell Chocolate Co. (Box 397)
  - Wandling Glove Co. TO Warren-Burnham Co. (Box 398)
  - Warren Commercial Club of Warren, Ohio TO Watkins (J.B.) Land Mortgage Co. (Box 399)
  - Watkins National Bank, Lawrence, Kan. TO Wentworth Manufacturing Co. (Box 400)
  - Wentworth Military Scientific & Literary Educational Co. TO Westchester First National Corp. (Box 401)
  - Westchester Lighting Co. TO Western Pacific Railroad Co. (Box 402)
  - Western Pacific Railroad Co. TO Western Union Telegraph Co (Box 403)
  - Western Union Telegraph Co. (Legal Materials) TO Westinghouse Electric & Manufacturing Co. (Box 404)
  - Westinghouse Electric & Manufacturing Co. TO Wheeling & Lake Erie Railroad Co (Box 405)
  - Wheeling, Lake Erie Railroad Co. TO Whitman & Barnes Inc. (Box 406)
  - Whitman Building Corp. TO Wilson & Co., Inc. (Box 407)
  - Wilson & Co., Inc. Wisconsin Central Railway Co. (Box 408)
  - Wisconsin Central Railway Co. TO Wisconsin Public Service Corp. (Box 409)
  - Wisconsin Public Service Corp. TO Wright Aeronautical Corp. (Box 410)
  - Wright & Taylor Distilling Corp. TO Zurn Industries, Inc. (Box 411)